<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mo Becher</title><link>https://becher.io/</link><description>Recent content on Mo Becher</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>CC BY-NC 4.0</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:05:18 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://becher.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sample Post</title><link>https://becher.io/posts/sample-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:05:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://becher.io/posts/sample-post/</guid><description>Hello World this is an example post, please just ignore it</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://becher.io/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://becher.io/about/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m a graphics and ai developer based in Berlin, currently working for UX3D GmbH on state of the art GPU projects and glTF, the next generation 3D file format.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://becher.io/cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://becher.io/cv/</guid><description>Profile Dedicated and communicative programmer with a background in Visual Computing, GPU Software and Machine Learning. Currently, in a lead developer role handling the intersection of product, team and customer satisfaction. Keen to solve challenging software problems in a friendly and diverse work environment.
Experience Lead Software Engineer - UX3D GmbH May 2020 - Present
Product Ownership of Gestaltor, a content creation application for the glTF file format, the main product of UX3D.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://becher.io/imprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://becher.io/imprint/</guid><description>Impressum (German law demands this)
Angaben gemäß § 5 TMG und verantwortlich für den Inhalt nach § 55 Abs. 2 RStV:
Moritz Becher Perleberger Str. 18 10559 Berlin Kontakt:
E-Mail: web@becher.io Haftungsausschluss: Haftung für Inhalte Die Inhalte unserer Seiten wurden mit größter Sorgfalt erstellt. Für die Richtigkeit, Vollständigkeit und Aktualität der Inhalte können wir jedoch keine Gewähr übernehmen. Als Diensteanbieter sind wir gemäß § 7 Abs.1 TMG für eigene Inhalte auf diesen Seiten nach den allgemeinen Gesetzen verantwortlich.</description></item></channel></rss>